<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Get Daily Diamonds FF Tips</string>

    <string name="ads_loader">Loading Ads....</string>
    <string name="fb_testing">f75de721-f449-47e1-bbd4-6d3a2e8962f5</string>


    <string name="des_correct_landing_point">➺ Choosing a landing point is only the first step to victory.
        \n\n➺ Although it may seem trivial, it is not.
        \n\n➺ Determining where to stare the game correctly.
        \n\n➺ The important thing is to choose a place that is isolated from other players, very close to the city, but not so close.
        \n\n➺ So, that best option is to fall from the town, observe where other people full and enter to explore.
        \n\n➺ It is very important that we don\'t expose ourselves too much before we don\'t have the proper equipment, especially
    when we are everywhere both quantity and quality are robbed, there will be players in many places.</string>

    <string name="correct_landing_point">Choose The Correct Landing Point</string>

    <string name="complate_game_archi">Complate in Game Achievements</string>
    <string name="des_complate_game_archi">➺ FF has a variety of in-game achievements that players can complete to earn rewards such as diamonds, gold coins, character skins, and weapon skins.
    \n\n➺ Achievements are categorized into different types,such as combat, survival, and teamwork.

    <font Textstyle="bold" color="#376e9d" size="18">\n\n➺ Here are some tips for completing in-game
    achievements in FF: </font>

    \n\n1. Check the achievement list: Open the achievement
    list and check which achievements are available.
    Focus on the ones that offer rewards you are
    interested in.

   \n\n2. Choose achievements that match your playable:
    Each achievement requires different skills and
    strategies, so choose the ones that match your
    playable.

    \n\n3. Set achievable goals: Some achievements require
    a lot of effort and time to complete, so set achievable
    goals and focus on completing them one at a time.

    \n\n4. Play with friends: Some achievements require you to
    play with friends or in a team. Playing with friends can
    make completing these achievements easier and more
    enjoyable.</string>

    <string name="miletary_site">Explore Military Sites</string>
    <string name="des_miletary_site">➺ If there is no enemy in sight, it is a good idea to explore attractions such as watch towers, containers,
    battle es or military tents.
        \n\n➺ In these places, there are usually a lot of loot.
    \n\n➺ It is not very wish to explore these areas from the beginning, but if we do it in the middle of the game, there will always be a lot to do. There will definitely be
    fewer players lurking to destroy us.
    \n\n➺ In such places, kits are usually found to improve bulletproof vests.
        \n\n➺ Please pay attention when exploring, because although you can wear a first-level vest, it is strongly recommended that you upgrade it as soon as possible.
        \n\n➺ The last player will always have powerful weapons.
    </string>


    <string name="complete_mission">Complete Mission</string>
    <string name="des_complete_mission">➺ FF offers a variety of missions that players can complete to earn rewards, including character
        vouchers, weapon skins, and diamonds.
        \n\n➺ The missions can be found in the missions section of the game and are updated regularly with new challenges and rewards.
        \n\n➺ There are different types of missions in FF, including daily missions, weekly missions, and event missions.
       \n\n➺ Daily missions reset every day and offer smaller rewards, while weekly missions reset every week and offer larger rewards. Event missions are tied to specific in-game events and offer unique rewards.

        <font Textstyle="bold" color="#376e9d" size="18">\n\nHere are some tips for completing missions in FF:</font>

        \n\n❖ Check the mission requirements:
        \n➺ Some missions have specific requirements, such as playing a certain game mode or using a specific character.
        \n➺ Make sure to check the requirements before starting the mission to avoid wasting time.

        \n\n❖ Play with friends:
        \n➺ Some missions require you to play with friends or in a team.
        \n➺ Playing with friends can make completing these missions easier and more enjoyable.

        \n\n❖ Complete multiple missions at once:

        \n➺ Some missions have similar objectives, so try to complete multiple missions at once to save time.</string>

    <string name="daily_login">Daily Login Rewards</string>
    <string name="des_daily_login"><font Textstyle="bold" color="#376e9d" size="18">Fire, here is some information about the daily login rewards:</font>

        \n\n➺ FF offers daily login rewards to players who log into the game on a daily basis.
        \n\n➺ These rewards can include various items such as character vouchers, weapon skins, and diamonds.
        \n\n➺ The rewards increase in value the more consecutive days you log in, up to a maximum of 30 days.
        \n\n➺ If you log in for 30 consecutive days, you can earn up to 100 diamonds as a reward.

        <font Textstyle="bold" color="#376e9d" size="18">\n\nHere is an example of the daily login rewards for a 7-day consecutive login:</font>
        \n\nDay 1: Character Voucher
        \nDay 2: Diamond Royal Voucher
        \nDay 3: Weapon Royal Voucher
        \nDay 4: Gold Royal Voucher
        \nDay 5: Pet Food
        \nDay 6: Memory Fragment
        \nDay 7: Weapon Skin

        \n\n\n➺ Please note that the daily login rewards can vary based on the region and the current in-game events.
        \n\n➺ It\'s always a good idea to check the in-game events section for the latest information on the daily login rewards.</string>

    <string name="participate_event">Participate in Game Events</string>
    <string name="des_participate_event">➺ In-game events are a great way to earn rewards and experience new content in FF.
        \n\n➺ The game regularly hosts events that allow you to complete tasks and challenges in exchange for rewards such as skins, characters, and other items.
       <font Textstyle="bold" color="#376e9d" size="18">\n\nHere are some tips for participating in in-game events in FF:</font>

        \n\n1. Check the events tab: The events tab in the main menu will show you all the ongoing events and their requirements.
        \n➺ Check this tab regularly to see what events are available and what rewards you can earn.
        \n\n2. Complete event tasks: Each event has specific tasks and challenges that you need to complete to earn rewards.
        \n➺ Make sure to complete all the tasks to maximize your rewards.
        \n\n3. Participate in limited-time events: Some events are only available for a limited time.
        \n➺ Make sure to participate in these events as soon as they become available to earn the maximum rewards.
        \n\n4. Use event items: Some events give you items that can only be used during the event.
        \n➺ Make sure to use these items to complete the event tasks and earn rewards.</string>

    <string name="use_vehicle">Use The Vehicle Carefully</string>
    <string name="des_use_vehicle">➺ These vehicles are used to quickly move to other places, where there are a lot of loot and can also pass the players we found on the road without players.
\n\n➺ If we make too much sound, other players will be able to hear us.
        \n\n➺ Therefore, Please be careful when using cars, trucks and motorcycles so as not to reveal our location.
</string>

    <string name="des_zombified">➺ The Zombified Samurai Bundle is FF’s most sought-after rare pack.
        \n\n➺ This pack was launched in 2019 when the game’s player base was significantly lower.
        \n\n➺ It\’s a personalization of the ever-popular Samurai Bundle.
        \n\n➺ The set includes a magnificent mask that is sure to terrify your opponents.
        \n\n➺ This pack is slightly unusual in the game, putting it at the eighth rank on this list of top rare packs in FF.</string>
    <string name="des_artic">➺ The Arctic Blue bundle was essentially accessible in the incubator section.
        \n\n➺ The players must rely on their good fortune.
        \n\n➺ To win, they’d have to spin.
        \n\n➺ Most gamers who were really excited about this package gave it their all, but they couldn’t afford the outcome, making this another unusual outfit.</string>
    <string name="des_greencriminal">➺ The Green Criminal outfit is the most sought-after package in the game.
        \n\n➺ Due to its extreme rarity, the bundle made it to the top of the list.
        \n\n➺ This set was available during a special event in the Store’s Redeem area, where players used “Lucky Stars” to redeem it.</string>
    <string name="des_bunny">➺ One of the rarest FF bundles is the warrior bunny bundle.
        \n\n➺ This fantastic bundle was highlighted at the Draw a Bunny event by the FF game makers.
        \n\n➺ To participate in this contest, all you have to do is draw a bunny’s face.
        \n\n➺ In this bundle, you will get these items.</string>
    <string name="des_crazy">➺ One of the least appealing skins on the list is this insane Panda pack.
        \n\n➺ The first skin to be included in the Magic Cube Elite Pack was the FF bundle.
        \n\n➺ Only one Magic Cube may be obtained from the Bundle.
        \n\n➺ The Skin is a simple black hoodie with a little black panda logo design.</string>
    <string name="des_galaxy">➺ A FF Incubator featured the Blue colored galaxy Dino Bundle as one of six Dino bundles (Dinosaur Suits).
        \n\n➺ It was taken out of the incubator after a few days.
        \n\n➺ Due to its high price and distinctive style, the Blue Dino package became one of the most sought-after.
        \n\n➺ Because the Blue Dino bundle was the most difficult to obtain, it became the rarest of all the outfits.
        \n\n➺ Despite the fact that the bundle has been in the game several times, it is still one of the rarest outfits.</string>
    <string name="des_electric">➺ The electric shock bundle is another item on our list.
        \n\n➺ This package was introduced in Season 2 of Garena FF.
        \n\n➺ The character’s hair is the most appealing aspect of this bundle.
        \n\n➺ When you wear this bundle, you will notice gleaming golden hair.</string>
    <string name="des_iron">➺ One of the rarest bundles in the FF is the iron blade bundle.
        \n\n➺ The ponytail hair of the iron blade bundle is its unique feature.
        \n\n➺ This hair can be combined with a variety of other bundles.
        \n\n➺ This bundle’s theme is also samurai.</string>
    <string name="des_purshade">➺ The top bundle on our list is purple shade, one of the most famous and rare FF bundles.
        \n\n➺ This collection is inspired by Korean animation.
        \n\n➺ White hair, a mask, a jacket, a pair of jeans, and shoes are included in this bundle.</string>
    <string name="des_sakura">➺ One of the most difficult to come by is the Sakura bundle in FF.
        \n\n➺ A result, every member of the gaming community is keeping an eye on the latest developments and leaks.</string>
    <string name="des_breakdance">➺ This bundle was available in the gold royal area of the lucky royal section last year and was quite popular during the Diwali wishing event.
        \n\n➺ The breakdancer bundle is back in the game, however only a few FF players can buy it with diamonds this time.</string>
    <string name="des_joker">➺ The Night Clown Joker Bundle is one of the most sought-after bundles in the game.</string>


    <string name="char_luna">➺ Luna\'s Fight-or-Flight ability is of great use to players who use weapons with slower fire rates.
        \n\n➺ With a quicker fire rate, players can empty their magazine much faster and deal more damage to their enemies.
        \n\n➺ The character\'s ability helps players enhance the weapon fire rate and increase movement speed, which helps in swift movement and better aim tracing in FF MAX.</string>
    <string name="char_iris">➺ The Iris character in the game is an expert at Walls of Ice and has a powerful capacity to brand and exterminate foes on the battlefield, so your enemies must be terrified.</string>
    <string name="char_patroa">➺ A-Patroa character extra special skill slot can be equipped with any skill on the account and is automatically unlocked upon getting the character</string>
    <string name="char_kenta">➺ Kenta character can create a front shield that can withstand all enemy attacks from the front.
        \n\n➺ He can now protect his teammates.</string>
    <string name="char_biebs">➺ J.Biebs has a special survival skill called Night Silence, helping players to overcome their opponents on the battlefield.
        \n\n➺ At its lowest level, Silence of Night allows users and their allies within 6 meters to block incoming damage using their EP.</string>
    <string name="char_dimitri">➺ Dimitri is the elder brother of Thiva.
        \n\n➺ In his daily life, he would spend most of his day at the lab developing new sound technology.
        \n\n➺ After he found his passion for music, he realized that helping the world and improving people\"s lives moving forward through his technological creations might be one of his dreams.</string>
    <string name="char_nairi">➺ Nairi\'s Ice Iron ability automatically heals the gloo walls after they have been deployed.
       \n\n➺ At level 1 of the ability, the gloo walls recover 20% of their durability every 20 seconds.</string>
    <string name="char_otho">➺ Otho is not a collaboration character or classic character.
        \n\n➺ It is a character that has been added to comics, which is the FF E-comics recently.
        \n\n➺ This character is a memory tech engineer from Polytech University.</string>
    <string name="char_thiva">➺ Thiva character At its initial level, the rescue speed is increased by 10%, and on successful rescue, the player recovers 15 HP in 5 seconds.
        \n\n➺ The rescue speed increases by 25%, and after rescuing the player recovers 40 HP in 5 seconds, at its max level.</string>
    <string name="char_tatsuya">➺ Tatsuya is known for his speed as he is the fastest among the playable characters in the game.
        \n\n➺ He is equipped with an active ability known as \'Rebel Rush\'.
        \n\n➺ This special survival ability helps him move forward with rapid speed.
        \n\n➺ Also, this skill can be accumulated for consecutive use.</string>
    <string name="char_homer">➺ Homer possesses the unique ability named \'Senses Shockwave \'.
       \n\n➺ Upon activation of the skill on the battlefield, it releases a drone towards the nearest enemy within a 100m frontal distance, creating a 5m-diameter pulse explosion which reduces movement speed by 10% and firing rate by 10%.</string>
    <string name="char_leon">➺ Leon is a university student and comes with extreme basketball skills.
        \n\n➺ The character comes with Buzzer Beater survival ability that allows players to recover HP after engagement in combat.</string>


    <string name="des_char_luna">➺ LUNA CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ Luna comes under the passive character list and is not bound by any time duration.
        \n\n➺ The character is inspired by the popular Thai actress “Yaya Urassaya.”
        \n\n➺ Luna features a special passive ability called Fight-or-Flight.
        \n\n➺ With the help of this ability, players can improve the firing rate of the weapon, and the movement speed also increases.
        \n\n➺ Players can use the character to use weapons that have great damage per hit but lack a rate of fire.
        \n\n➺ The character is suitable for assault rifles and shotguns with heavy damage, and with Luna, the rate of fire will be enhanced.
        \n\n➺ The character will be available in the character store after the in-game event ends.</string>
    <string name="des_char_iris">➺ IRIS CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ Iris has two crucial skill aspects, namely the ability to mark enemies and penetrate the Gloo Wall.
        \n\n➺ Once the skill is active, players only need to shoot the Gloo Wall to activate the enemy marker located behind the Gloo Wall.
        \n\n➺ The skill of Iris is able to attack the marked enemy behind the Gloo Wall.
        \n\n➺ Iris\' skill can penetrate 5 Gloo Walls even in a parallel position.
        \n\n➺ So even enemies behind 5 Gloo Walls can still be attacked by Iris.
        \n\n➺ At the maximum level, the cooldown of the skill is only 55 seconds.
        \n\n➺ Can even beat Skyler and Chrono.</string>
    <string name="des_char_patroa">➺ A-PATROA CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ The Boss (Anitta) is a strong and confident woman who has a music store and sensory experiences in a dangerous neighborhood.
        \n\n➺ In addition, your store serves as a safe space for anyone seeking help.
        \n\n➺ The experiences offered by the store are not only a form of fun, but also a way to help people.
        \n\n➺ Patroa owns a music store that serves not only as a space for socializing and entertainment in a particularly dangerous region, but also as a shelter for people in vulnerable situations, especially women.
        \n\n➺ Space allows these women to explore and experience freedom and security, free from judgment.
        \n\n➺ In the store it is possible to enjoy an experience technologically created by her that allows them to fully immerse themselves in emotions, memories and experiences.
        \n\n➺ The experience is called RIO , as is the store.</string>
    <string name="des_char_kenta">➺ KENTA CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ Kenta does not have a unique ability, but can be equipped with an existing ability.
        \n\n➺ Kenta is a recommended character for beginners, they can equip and experiment.
        \n\n➺ Use against explosives: Kenta’s ability proves very effective against grenades, launchers, and others.
        \n\n➺ Using his shield power, players can tackle any combat including any explosives.
        \n\n➺ Purely defensive: The area of the force field is quite large, so it protects teammates very effectively.
        \n\n➺ The time to use Swordsman’s Wrath is also quite long.
        \n\n➺ However, it automatically disappears when Kenta takes any shot.
        \n\n➺ No one can attack through a force field: Swordsman’s Wrath blocks about half of enemy Weapons damage.
        \n\n➺ That renders nearly every attack ineffective.</string>
    <string name="des_char_biebs">➺ J.BIEBS CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ J.Biebs is a man who wants to unite a fractured world. Through his childhood experiences, he learned that the answer to people’s problems is not money or power, but the actual connection between people.
        \n\n➺ He then decided to use his singing skills to dedicate his life to reunite the world.
        \n\n➺ Sentinel allows users and their allies to block damage using EP, and the amount of EP deducted from allies will be added to the user’s EP.
        \n\n➺ The range of this ability is 6 meters at the lowest level, while the damage percentage prevented is 7%.</string>
    <string name="des_char_dimitri">➺ DIMITRI CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ Dimitri is one of the recommended characters for players who prefer healing skills.
        \n\n➺ He has an active skill called Healing Heartbeat.
        \n\n➺ The skill allows its users to create 3.5m healing zones.
        \n\n➺ Players who are inside the zone can recover 3HP/sec.
        \n\n➺ If a player or teammate is down, they can self recover to get up.
        \n\n➺ At its initial level, the skill lasts for 20 seconds and has a 85-second
        \n\n➺ Players can upgrade their character level by using EXP cards and playing more ranked matches.
        \n\n➺ It will help them to unlock further upgrade levels of the character with improved skills.
        \n\n❖  Level 1: Duration increases by 11 seconds and cooldown reduces to 80 seconds.
        \n\n❖  Level 2: Duration increases by 12 seconds and the cooldown reduces to 75 seconds.
        \n\n❖  Level 3: Duration increases by 13 seconds and the cooldown reduces to 70 seconds.
        \n\n❖  Level 4: Duration increases by 14 seconds and the cooldown reduces to 65 seconds.
        \n\n❖  Level 5: Duration increases by 15 seconds and the cooldown reduces to 60 seconds.</string>
    <string name="des_char_nairi">➺ NAIRI CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ In FF, Nairi’s ability gets activated automatically.
        \n\n➺ He has a special survival ability that the deployed Gloo walls will recover a certain amount of current durability every 1 sec when damage is taken.
        \n\n➺ Also, the user equipping this skill will get increased damage on Gloo walls while shooting from any AR Weapons.</string>
    <string name="des_char_otho">➺ OTHO CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ Otho is not yet available in the in-game store.
        \n\n➺ He is currently available to players only if they make a purchase during the ongoing top-up event.
        \n\n➺ In this event players need to top-up certain amount of diamonds to get Otho for free and if players want they can also get the Otho character bundle.
        \n\n➺ Otho’s ability includes Memory Mist.
        \n\n➺ When users eliminate enemies, Otho can reveal the locations of other foes within a 25-meter radius.
        \n\n➺ He can then share this information with the other teammates.
        \n\n➺ As the player advances, the range to which Otho can use his ability also increases.
        \n\n➺ The maximum potential for the character is 50 meters.</string>
    <string name="des_char_thiva">➺ THIVA CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ Thiva is the little brother of Dimitri.\n\nHe was innately talented and played music throughout his childhood.
        \n\n➺ He really wants to help the world and improve people\'s lives but believes the best way to do that is to reach the individual with a true message through his music.
        \n\n➺ His ability is called Vital Vibes, improving the help-up speed by 5% at the first level.
        Additionally, players who revived will receive 15 health points in the next five seconds.
        The ability considerably improves as the level rises.
        \n\n➺ At the maximum level of 6, users’ help-up speed will be buffed to 20%, while the HP recovered after rescue stands at 40.</string>
    <string name="des_char_tatsuya">➺ TATSUYA CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ Tatsuya’s ability is active.
        \n\n➺ Players will get to use the ability for a limited duration only and it requires manual activation.
        \n\n➺ He can move forward at a rapid speed for a limited duration.
        \n\n➺ This ability will be a game changer when players will need to retreat from an intense fight.
        \n\n➺ Tatsuya can move forward at a rapid speed for 0.5 seconds.
        \n\n➺ The skill can be accumulated for consecutive uses (Up to 2 times).
        \n\n➺ It has a cool-down time as it is an active skill. The Cooldown is 40 seconds.
        \n\n➺ Moreover, if anyone uses the skill consecutively, they will face an additional 5 seconds of cool down between uses.
        \n\n➺ Players can upgrade Tatsuya’s skill by using memory fragments which will eventually lower the cooldown to 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="des_char_homer">➺ HOMER CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ Homer is a blind man who is also an assassin.
        \n\n➺ He is the founder of Griza gang.
        \n\n➺ The character comes with a special survival ability, known as Sense Shockwave.
        \n\n➺ With this, Homer is able to release a drone to the nearest frontal enemy, creating a 5m-diameter pulse explosion, which reduces enemy movement speed and firing speed.
        \n\n➺ He can release the drone at the closest frontal enemy, creating a 5 meter diameter pulse burst that reduces the enemy\'s movement speed and firing speed and deals 25 damage to them.
        \n\n➺ The duration of the slow effect is 5 seconds. The drone\'s search area is 100 meters in front, which is quite large.
        \n\n➺ Homer\'s ability in FF is an active skill and can only be used for combos with other passive skills.
        \n\n➺ Overall, since the duration of the drone effect is quite short (5 seconds), it is the most effective in rusher combos.</string>
    <string name="des_char_leon">➺ LEON CHARACTERS INFORMATION :
        \n\n➺ With Leon\'s ability being a passive skill, you can combine it with pretty much all skills in the game, from long to close range.
        \n\n➺ It is very effective against chip damage - a combination of Buzzer Beater and EP could get you to full pretty quickly.
        \n\n➺ Overall, Assaulter and Sniper builds are the best for Leon, as you can get 100 -> 0 rather quick in close range fights.
        \n\n➺ Leon is another character that has been added to FF, and has a unique ability named Buzzer Beater.
        \n\n➺ He recovers HP after surviving a combat encounter, and this can turn out to be helpful during aggressive gameplay.
        \n\n➺ The exact details about the HP recovered at every level have been provided below:
        \n\n❖  Level 1\nHP recovery:5
        \n\n❖  Level 2\nHP recovery: 10
        \n\n❖  Level 3\nHP recovery: 15
        \n\n❖  Level 4\nHP recovery: 20
        \n\n❖  Level 5\nHP recovery: 25
        \n\n❖  Level 6\nHP recovery: 30"</string>

    <string name="angry_emote">➺ The Angry emote features a character looking furious.
        \n\n➺ It is often used to express frustration after a defeat or to intimidate an opponent.</string>
    <string name="applause_emote">➺ The Applause emote features a character clapping their hands in applause.
        \n\n➺ It is often used to show appreciation for a teammate\'s efforts or to congratulate someone on their victory.</string>
    <string name="bye_emote">➺ BYE emote available in the popular mobile game FF.
        \n\n➺ When a player uses this emote, their character will wave their hand in a gesture of farewell, while the text BYE appears on the screen.</string>
    <string name="dance_emote">➺ The Dance emote features a character performing a dance.
        \n\n➺ There are several different dance emotes available in FF, each with its own unique style.</string>
    <string name="firework_emote">➺ It is a celebratory emote that features a character setting off fireworks.
        \n\n➺ This emote is often used to celebrate a victory or to add a fun and festive touch to the game.</string>
    <string name="flex_emote">➺ The Flex emote features a character flexing their muscles in a show of strength.
        \n\n➺ It is often used to show off physical fitness or to intimidate an opponent.</string>
    <string name="heart_emote">➺ This emote features a character forming a heart shape with their hands, often used to express love, affection, or gratitude towards teammates or other players in the game.
        \n\n➺ To use the Heart emote, you can go to the emote section in the game and select it from your emote inventory.</string>
    <string name="hello_emote">➺ The Hello emote features a character waving their hand in greeting.
        \n\n➺ It is often used to say hello to other players at the beginning of a match or to greet someone in the game lobby.</string>
    <string name="thumpup_emote">➺ The Thumbs Up emote features a character giving a thumbs up gesture.
        \n\n➺ It is often used to show approval or to signal that everything is good.</string>
    <string name="hug_emote">➺ The Hug emote features a character giving a warm hug to someone.
        \n\n➺ It is often used to show appreciation for a teammate or to express sympathy for a defeated opponent.</string>
    <string name="kiss_emote">➺ This emote features a character blowing a kiss with a heart animation.
        \n\n➺ It is often used to express love, affection, or gratitude towards teammates or other players in the game.
        \n\n➺ To use the Kiss emote, you can go to the emote section in the game and select it from your emote inventory.</string>
    <string name="laughing_emote">➺ The Laughing emote features a character laughing hysterically.
        \n\n➺ It is often used to taunt an opponent after a kill or to express amusement at a funny moment in the game.</string>


    <string name="apoca_des">➺ Appearance: The Apocalypse Parachute features a dark and rugged design, with a black and gray color scheme and a skull and crossbones emblem.
        \n\n➺ Durability: The Apocalypse Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.
        \n\n➺ Deployment: The Apocalypse Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the\"jump\" button twice while in the air.
        \n\n➺ Speed: The Apocalypse Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.
        \n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Apocalypse Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.
        \n\n➺ Customization: The Apocalypse Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Apocalypse Parachute provides a unique and intimidating appearance for players, which can help them stand out and intimidate enemies.
        \n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Apocalypse Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and it can even attract more attention from enemies due to its distinctive appearance.</string>
    <string name="beach_des">➺ Beach Party Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Beach Party Parachute features a colorful and festive design, with a bright pink and blue color scheme and beach-themed decorations, such as palm trees, beach balls, and umbrellas.\n The Beach Party Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Beach Party Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Beach Party Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Beach Party Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Beach Party Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Beach Party Parachute provides a fun and playful appearance for players, which can help them stand out and lift the mood of the game.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Beach Party Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its bright colors and decorations can attract more attention from enemies.</string>
    <string name="circus_des">➺ Circus Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Circus Parachute features a colorful and whimsical design, with a red and white striped pattern and circus-themed decorations, such as clowns, elephants, and circus tents.\n\n➺ Durability: The Circus Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Circus Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Circus Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Circus Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Circus Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Circus Parachute provides a fun and lighthearted appearance for players, which can help them stand out and add some humor to the game.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Circus Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its bright colors and decorations can attract more attention from enemies.</string>
    <string name="panda_des">➺ Panda Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Panda Parachute features a cute and adorable design, with a black and white color scheme and a panda face on the top of the parachute.\n\n➺ Durability: The Panda Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Panda Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Panda Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Panda Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Panda Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Panda Parachute provides a cute and charming appearance for players, which can help them stand out and attract positive attention from other players.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Panda Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its distinctive appearance can make players easier to spot by enemies.</string>
    <string name="dragne_des">➺ Dragne Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Dragne Parachute features a fearsome and epic design, with a red and black color scheme and dragon-themed decorations, such as dragon scales and wings.\n\n➺ Durability: The Dragne Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Dragne Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Dragne Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Dragne Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Dragne Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Dragne Parachute provides a menacing and powerful appearance for players, which can intimidate and impress other players.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Dragne Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its distinctive appearance can make players easier to spot by enemies.</string>
    <string name="dragon_des">➺ Dragon Slayer Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Dragon Slayer Parachute features a fearsome and epic design, with a red and black color scheme and dragon-themed decorations, such as dragon scales and wings.\n\n➺ Durability: The Dragon Slayer Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Dragon Slayer Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Dragon Slayer Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Dragon Slayer Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Dragon Slayer Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Dragon Slayer Parachute provides a menacing and powerful appearance for players, which can intimidate and impress other players.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Dragon Slayer Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its distinctive appearance can make players easier to spot by enemies.</string>
    <string name="hip_des">➺ Hip Hop Parachute Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Hip Hop Parachute features a stylish and urban design, with a black and gold color scheme and graffiti-style lettering.\n\n➺ Durability: The Hip Hop Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Hip Hop Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Hip Hop Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Hip Hop Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Hip Hop Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Hip Hop Parachute provides a cool and trendy appearance for players, which can help them stand out and add some style to the game.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Hip Hop Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its bright colors and decorations can attract more attention from enemies.</string>
    <string name="cobra_des">➺ Cobra Parachute Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Cobra Parachute features a colorful and whimsical design, with a red and white striped pattern and circus-themed decorations, such as clowns, elephants, and circus tents.\n\n➺ Durability: The Cobra Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Cobra Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Cobra Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Cobra Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Cobra Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Cobra Parachute provides a fun and lighthearted appearance for players, which can help them stand out and add some humor to the game.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Cobra Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its bright colors and decorations can attract more attention from enemies.</string>
    <string name="panthera_des">➺ Panthera Parachute Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Panthera Parachute features a black and yellow color scheme and a fierce panther design that covers the entire parachute.\n\n➺ Durability: The Panthera Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Panthera Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Panthera Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Panthera Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Panthera Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Panthera Parachute provides a fearsome and impressive appearance for players, which can intimidate and impress other players.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Panthera Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its distinctive appearance can make players easier to spot by enemies.</string>
    <string name="santa_des">➺ Santa Parachute Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Santa Parachute features a red and white color scheme and a festive design with Santa Claus and snowflakes.\n\n➺ Durability: The Santa Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Santa Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Santa Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Santa Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Santa Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Santa Parachute provides a festive and cheerful appearance for players during the Christmas season, which can add some holiday spirit to the game.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Santa Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its distinctive appearance can make players easier to spot by enemies. Additionally, it is only available during the Christmas season, which limits its usefulness throughout the rest of the year.</string>
    <string name="shark_des">➺ Shark Attack Parachute Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Shark Attack Parachute features a blue and white color scheme with a shark design that covers the entire parachute. The shark\'s jaws are open and appear to be attacking its prey.\n\n➺ Durability: The Shark Attack Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is the same as the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Shark Attack Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Shark Attack Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Shark Attack Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Shark Attack Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Shark Attack Parachute provides a unique and intimidating appearance for players, which can make them stand out and potentially intimidate other players.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Shark Attack Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its distinctive appearance can make players easier to spot by enemies.</string>
    <string name="winer_des">➺ Winerlands Parachute Parachute Details :\n\n➺ Appearance: The Winerlands Parachute features a red and white color scheme and a festive design with Winerlands Claus and snowflakes.\n\n➺ Durability: The Winerlands Parachute has a durability of 100 points, which is higher than the standard parachute\'s durability.\n\n➺ Deployment: The Winerlands Parachute is deployed the same way as the standard parachute, by tapping the \"jump\" button twice while in the air.\n\n➺ Speed: The Winerlands Parachute has the same descent speed as the standard parachute, at 30 m/s.\n\n➺ Landing: Players can control their landing by steering the Winerlands Parachute towards a safe landing spot, just like with the standard parachute.\n\n➺ Customization: The Winerlands Parachute cannot be further customized or upgraded, and its appearance cannot be changed.\n\nAdvantages: The Winerlands Parachute provides a festive and cheerful appearance for players during the Christmas season, which can add some holiday spirit to the game.\n\n➺ Disadvantages: The Winerlands Parachute does not provide any functional advantage over the standard parachute, and its distinctive appearance can make players easier to spot by enemies. Additionally, it is only available during the Christmas season, which limits its usefulness throughout the rest of the year.</string>

    <string name="derki_des">➺ Dreki is a cute mini dragon with big twinkle eyes, two small wings, short arms &amp; legs, and a burning tail.
        \n\n➺ Just like all other pets, Dreki also comes with three actions which are as follows:
        \n\n➺ Celebrate, Play, and Show.</string>
    <string name="dragon_pet_des">➺ The new pet that has been introduced in the Pet section of the OB26 server is known as DRAGON Pet, and it has a great ability to offer to its owner.</string>
    <string name="robo_des">➺ Robo is a robot-based pet that players can buy in FF. This pet possesses a skill called \'Wall Enforcement\'. This skill adds a shield to the gloo wall, thereby adding 60 additional HP. It increases to 80 when the pet reaches Level 5.</string>
    <string name="moony_des">➺ The newest addition, \‘Moony\’ is an alien pet.
        \n\n➺ Even though Moony is not from this world, but he loves everything about us.
        \n\n➺ Similar to other pets of the game, Moony also comes with a special ability.
        \n\n➺ Pet’s special skill is named ‘Paranormal Protection.</string>
    <string name="ottero_des">➺ The ability of Ottero Pet In FF is pretty unique because whenever you increase your HP, this pet will automatically increase your EP by using the Treatment Weapons or the Med Kit.
        \n\n➺ Therefore this set stays the best in FF for many of the players.</string>
    <string name="panda_pet_des">➺ The Detective Panda is one of the cutest pets available in the FF game.</string>
    <string name="poring_des">➺ The skill of Poring pet increases one durability of health and armour every three seconds.
        \n\n➺ This ability sees an improvement in Level 5 of the pet, and its durability increases every two seconds.</string>
    <string name="falco_des">➺ Falco is useful for reaching air distances quickly at the start of a game which is exceptionally useful in Ranked games where the first to pick up a weapon makes the call.</string>
    <string name="shiba_des">➺ Shiba is a pet based on a dog. Shiba has a skill called \'Mushroom Sense\'.</string>
    <string name="waggor_des">➺ Mr. Waggor is a pet that can be obtained only through events or direct purchase through the store.
        \n\n➺ Its ability is called {Smooth Gloo} which provides the player with {1|1|2} Gloo wall every {120|100|80} seconds if no Gloo wall is in the inventory.</string>
    <string name="spirit_des">➺ Spirit Fox has an ability called Well Fed.
        \n\n➺ The ability can restore 4 extra HPs when using a health pack at its default level (level 1).
        \n\n➺ When it is maximized to pet level 7 and skill level 3, Spirit Fox can restore an extra 10 HP when using a health pack.</string>
    <string name="rockie_des">➺ Rockie pet that is mostly used by players who have the Time Turner active skill.
        \n\n➺ Rockie is probably one of the most used pets in FF by players who have active skills.
        \n\n➺ Rockie\'s skill is called Stay Chill and what it does is decrease the cooldown time of an active skill by 15%.</string>


    <!--    <string name="derki_des_info">The Apocalypse Parachute features a dark and rugged design, with a black and gray color scheme and a skull and crossbones emblem.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="dragon_pet_des_info">The Beach Party Parachute features a colorful and festive design, with a bright pink and blue color scheme and beach-themed decorations, such as palm trees, beach balls, and umbrellas.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="robo_des_info">The Circus Parachute features a colorful and whimsical design, with a red and white striped pattern and circus-themed decorations, such as clowns, elephants, and circus tents.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="moony_des_info">The Panda Parachute features a cute and adorable design, with a black and white color scheme and a panda face on the top of the parachute.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="ottero_des_info">The Dragne Parachute features a fearsome and epic design, with a red and black color scheme and dragon-themed decorations, such as dragon scales and wings.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="panda_pet_des_info">The Dragon Slayer Parachute features a fearsome and epic design, with a red and black color scheme and dragon-themed decorations, such as dragon scales and wings.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="poring_des_info">The Hip Hop Parachute features a stylish and urban design, with a black and gold color scheme and graffiti-style lettering.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="falco_des_info">The Cobra Parachute features a colorful and whimsical design, with a red and white striped pattern and circus-themed decorations, such as clowns, elephants, and circus tents.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="shiba_des_info">The Panthera Parachute features a black and yellow color scheme and a fierce panther design that covers the entire parachute. </string>-->
    <!--    <string name="waggor_des_info">The Santa Parachute features a red and white color scheme and a festive design with Santa Claus and snowflakes.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="spirit_des_info">The Shark Attack Parachute features a blue and white color scheme with a shark design that covers the entire parachute. The shark\'s jaws are open and appear to be attacking its prey.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="rockie_des_info">The Winerlands Parachute features a red and white color scheme and a festive design with Winerlands Claus and snowflakes.</string>-->

    <string name="motor_des">➺ It is the smallest vehicle of the game and can be used for going through narrower areas.
        \n\n➺ I would call it the vehicle for a player, even though it has a seating capacity of 2 and also has lower armor.
        \n\n➺ It makes you open for directly taking hits from all directions.</string>
    <string name="minicooper_des">➺ The Mini Cooper car is the best vehicle in the game, as it has a top speed of 136 km/hr and a capacity of two people.
        \n\n➺ This vehicle is also very durable and can be used to travel faster and safely during matches.</string>
    <string name="monster_des">➺ Monster trucks appear from an airdrop after the 5 minutes of the game.
        \n\n➺ It has high armor and can be used for travel through difficult terrain.
        \n\n➺ I would recommend you not to use it permanently but can be used for finding other vehicles.
        \n\n➺ Allows the enemies to hit at you directly.</string>
    <string name="helicopter_des">➺ Helicopters provide a tactical advantage by allowing players to quickly travel to different areas of the map and providing a high vantage point for spotting enemies.</string>
    <string name="amphibious_des">➺ The amphibious vehicle can be used on both the surfaces: land and water.
        \n\n➺ This is the vehicle with low armor and exposes you to direct hits from the enemies.</string>
    <string name="police_des">➺ It is one of the safest and fastest vehicles in the game in which enemies can hardly hit you.
        \n\n➺ If available, I would recommend using only this vehicle (if possible) because even if the enemy has enabled Auto-aiming, it won’t let them directly hit you, unlike other vehicles.</string>
    <string name="jeep_des">➺ Just like Monster truck, Jeep is also capable of traveling through difficult terrain.
       \n\n➺ After Monster Truck, it is the vehicle with most HP in the game that makes it easy for you to escape from the enemy’s range.
       \n\n➺ But if you are facing towards the enemy, then auto-aiming can allow to hit you directly.</string>
    <string name="pickup_des">➺ Pickup Truck is the standard vehicle of FF.
        \n\n➺ It is also one of the safest and fastest vehicles of the game like Sports Car.
        \n\n➺ It comes with medium armor and maximum speed.
       \n\n➺ After sports Car, I would keep it in preference because Sports Car and Pickup Truck are the only vehicles of the game that don’t let the enemies direct hit you.</string>
    <string name="sportcar_des">➺ The sports car is the best vehicle in the game, as it has a top speed of 136 km/hr and a capacity of two people.
        \n\n➺ This vehicle is also very durable and can be used to travel faster and safely during matches.</string>
    <string name="tuktuk_des">➺ Tuk-Tuk is the slowest vehicle of the game and comes with lower armor.
        \n\n➺ I would recommend it to use only in an urgent situation like reaching the safe zone or escaping from enemies in open grounds.
        \n\n➺ It also allows enemies to hit you directly.</string>

    <string name="motor_info">➺ Motorbike Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 300
        \n\n❖  Speed: 108 km/h
        \n\n❖  Safety: 40%
        \n\n❖  Torque: 1500
        \n\n❖  Seating Capacity: 2
        \n\n❖  Curves: 40
        \n\n❖  Velocity: 60</string>
    <string name="minicooper_info">➺ Mini Cooper Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 400
        \n\n❖  Speed: 136 km/h
        \n\n❖  Safety: 94%
        \n\n❖  Torque: 4400
        \n\n❖  Seating Capacity: 2
        \n\n❖  Curves: 20
        \n\n❖  Velocity: 75</string>
    <string name="monster_info">➺ Motorbike Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 800
        \n\n❖  Speed: 112 km/h
        \n\n❖  Safety: 70%
        \n\n❖  Torque: 8000
        \n\n❖  Seating Capacity: 4
        \n\n❖  Curves: 15
        \n\n❖  Velocity: 45</string>
    <string name="helicopter_info">➺ Helicopters Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 300
        \n\n❖  Spawn Locations: Helicopters can spawn randomly at various locations on the map, including airfields, military bases, and other designated helicopter spawn points.
        \n\n❖  Capacity: Each helicopter can accommodate up to four players, including the pilot.
        \n\n❖  Speed: Helicopters are one of the fastest modes of transportation in the game and can reach a top speed of 120 km/h.
        \n\n❖  Health Points: Helicopters have a total of 1000 health points and can be destroyed by enemy gunfire or explosive devices.
        \n\n❖  Controls: The pilot can control the helicopter\'s altitude and speed using the left joystick, while the right joystick is used to control the direction of flight.
        \n\n❖  Fuel: Helicopters consume fuel while in flight and will eventually run out if not refueled.Players can find fuel cans scattered across the map to refuel the helicopter.
        \n\n❖  Noise: Helicopters make a loud noise while in flight, which can alert other players to their presence.
        \n\n❖  Advantages: Helicopters provide a tactical advantage by allowing players to quickly travel to different areas of the map and providing a high vantage point for spotting enemies.
        \n\n❖  Disadvantages: Helicopters are relatively large and can be an easy target for enemy players, especially if flying at low altitudes. They also consume fuel quickly, making them a limited resource.</string>
    <string name="amphibious_info">➺ Amphibious Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 300
        \n\n❖  Speed: 100 km/h
        \n\n❖  Safety: 20%
        \n\n❖  Torque: 1400
        \n\n❖  Seating Capacity: 2
        \n\n❖  Curves: 15
        \n\n❖  Velocity: 40</string>
    <string name="police_info">➺ Police Car Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 400
        \n\n❖  Speed: 136 km/h
        \n\n❖  Safety: 95%
        \n\n❖  Torque: 4600
        \n\n❖  Seating Capacity: 2
        \n\n❖  Curves: 20
        \n\n❖  Velocity: 80</string>
    <string name="jeep_info">➺ Jeep Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 500
        \n\n❖  Speed: 102 km/h
        \n\n❖  Safety: 20%
        \n\n❖  Torque: 2900
        \n\n❖  Seating Capacity: 4
        \n\n❖  Curves: 15
        \n\n❖  Velocity: 40</string>
    <string name="pickup_info">➺ Pickup Truck Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 400
        \n\n❖  Speed: 138 km/h
        \n\n❖  Safety: 85%
        \n\n❖  Seating Capacity: 2100
        \n\n❖  Curves: 12
        \n\n❖  Velocity: 55</string>
    <string name="sportcar_info">➺ Sports Car Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 400
        \n\n❖  Speed: 136 km/h
        \n\n❖  Safety: 95%
        \n\n❖  Torque: 4600
        \n\n❖  Seating Capacity: 2
        \n\n❖  Curves: 20
        \n\n❖  Velocity: 80</string>
    <string name="tuktuk_info">➺ Tuk-Tuk Vehicles Information :
        \n\n❖  HP: 300
        \n\n❖  Speed: 81 km/h
        \n\n❖  Safety: 10%
        \n\n❖  Torque: 1200
        \n\n❖  Seating Capacity:3
        \n\n❖  Curves: 15
        \n\n❖  Velocity: 35</string>
    <string name="get_diamond_tips">Get Diamond Tips</string>
    <string name="pets">Pets</string>
    <string name="derki_pet">DERKI PET</string>
    <string name="dragon_pet">DRAGON PET</string>
    <string name="robo_pet">ROBO PET</string>
    <string name="moony_pet">MOONY PET</string>
    <string name="ottero_pet">OTTERO PET</string>
    <string name="panda_pet">PANDA PET</string>
    <string name="poring_pet">PORING PET</string>
    <string name="shiba_pet">SHIBA PET</string>
    <string name="mr_waggor_pet">MR. WAGGOR PET</string>
    <string name="spirit_fox">SPIRIT FOX</string>
    <string name="emotes">Emotes</string>
    <string name="vehicle">Vehicle</string>
    <string name="vehicle_details">Vehicle Details</string>
    <string name="motorbike_vehicles">Motorbike Vehicles</string>
    <string name="mini_cooper_vehicles">Mini Cooper Vehicles</string>
    <string name="monster_truck_vehicles">Monster Truck Vehicles</string>
    <string name="helicopter_vehicles">Helicopter Vehicles</string>
    <string name="police_car_vehicles">Police Car Vehicles</string>
    <string name="tuk_tuk_vehicles">Tuk-Tuk Vehicles</string>
    <string name="emotes_details">Emotes Details</string>
    <string name="angry">ANGRY</string>
    <string name="applause">APPLAUSE</string>
    <string name="bye_bye">BYE BYE</string>
    <string name="dance">DANCE</string>
    <string name="flex">FLEX</string>
    <string name="hello">HELLO</string>
    <string name="hug">HUG</string>
    <string name="parachute">Parachute</string>
    <string name="parachute_details">Parachute Details</string>
    <string name="apocalypse_parachute">Apocalypse Parachute</string>
    <string name="beach_party_parachute">BEACH PARTY PARACHUTE</string>
    <string name="circus_parachute">CIRCUS PARACHUTE</string>
    <string name="hip_hop_parachute">HIP HOP PARACHUTE</string>
    <string name="panda_parachute">PANDA PARACHUTE</string>
    <string name="santa_parachute">SANTA PARACHUTE</string>
    <string name="shark_attech_parachute">SHARK ATTECH PARACHUTE</string>
    <string name="characters">Characters</string>
    <string name="character_details">Character Details</string>
    <string name="bundles">Bundles</string>
    <string name="bundles_details">Bundles Details</string>


</resources>